so my life has been drastically impacted
by the internet and online communities
and so that is this video because it
inspires my mission in the world
Craigslist has been responsible for my
last serious relationship a lot of other
less like more minor relationships a few
of my best friends I've met through
Craigslist by putting up I put up this
goal-setting group a decade ago and one
of the people that answered is one of my
best friends to this day she is amazing
amazing piece of my life and my
ex-boyfriend who's an amazing piece of
my life both of whom I wouldn't have met
through it would not through Craigslist
I've had a lot of roommates I have met
nearly all of them through Craigslist
when I was given the capacity to be the
one to find my roommate how can be more
compatible rather than them going
through my landlord and they are
I mean who you live with changes in your
life no matter whether it's a good or
bad experience and I've left out that
almost all of those many very good
experiences and a handful of them have
become lifelong friends I
so Craigslist is one one thing that has
greatly changed my life the other thing
is Facebook groups when I became a
parent and I wasn't really able to go
out of the house as much with both a
newborn and I'll suggest my health
challenges in realizing that I can't
deal with the sensory input of the
outside world my world became very
insular and as someone who needed to
like run to everything by someone else
so I could kind of gauge it with my
inner filter sound understand that's
what I was doing I had these amazing
parenting groups that I was part of
every single one of my health challenges
has a Facebook group so when I need to
get advice on that specific thing or if
I have a new thing that arises like
which one does it fall under wait let's
ask the single side of deaf community
let's ask the autistic community let's
ask the ATD community it's ask the
acoustic neuroma community but
I got kicked out of that one for
questioning the supreme leader um I'm
just so grateful for the internet and
what it's brought to my life and these
especially Craigslist and the Facebook
groups now there's game B in the
Facebook group and I don't think I've
met half the people I have met if it
hadn't been for for that group because
the the Twitter game B thing just
doesn't work for from my brain but the
groups like I've seen people step up and
be there for people they have never met
before they've had conversations in a
Facebook group but then someone doesn't
have somebody to like watch their kid
for a week while they're in the hospital
and people step up and help them one of
the mothers was dying of cancer
it's now passed away and the amount that
the community stepped up and the
integral part of the community that she
was to watch people you know gather
around finding like answers to questions
what is this toy where can I find this
toy because it's my kids favorite and
we've lost it
crowdfunding and crowdsourcing and just
made me see the people when given the
option are good we want to help each
other we want to do kindness and even
one of the groups kind of was this a way
for people to help each other who were
who were under the poverty line like you
could request groceries you could
request certain items and there was a
bit of a scandal in there that the
people who ran it were like taking more
money and doing the stuff but even in
that even in the like not-so-great part
of humanity there was still right the
reason they were able to do that was by
tapping into all the goodness of
everyone else so let's not discount the
goodness of everyone else just because
somebody skewed it to their own best
interest because we can have both we can
do both we can create systems that
aren't as easy to manipulate and still
tap into the goodness of humanity and in
so doing I can see all the ways that the
Internet is powerful and can connect us
and enhance
our good nature and how it can do the
opposite and I have now figured out how
we can have it do much more of the good
with much less of the bad and a big
piece of that was seeing the blessings
that both Craigslist and these Facebook
groups had on my life and the lives of
people around me